This Monster Wants to Eat Me
Episode 1
A Girl Who Seeks Death Waits by the Sea
Snooze
Alarm
Stop
Call me if you need anything, dear.
Good night, take care.
Thanks for worrying about me.
Good night, Auntie.
Read
I don't think I'll make it back in time for the anniversary this year. I'm really sorry.
Seeing you in high school now would make your parents up in heaven so proud.
I'll be fine.
Good luck at work.
Miko
sorry, running late today!
head to school w/o me (>~< emoji)
Miko
stay safe!
I mean it! and sorry again (water emoji)
Ms. Takano is super scary
Mr. Yamashita (gym teacher)
is also hella scary
YEEEAH!!
Shiomi High School
Miko
shoot! I think I got a fever :<
sorry if I'm not there tomorrow
I'll text you tomorrow morning!
really sorry (pray emoji)
Take care
Read
Today
yep, stuck at home (sad face)
go ahead w/o me
were you okay by yourself?
be careful on the way home
Sowwy
Squelch...
So rude!
The Sunlit Beast and the Festival Song
Episode 2