When I close my eyes,
I hear the sound of the waves...
See the deep blue of the sea...
Amid hollow days, permeated by the invisible smell
of an unending summer...
I met a girl
with eyes like the sea.
And so it began.
I just... don't want to go.
Hey, good morning!
Good morning.
Family outing today?
Wait for me, Big Bro!
Hurry up! We're gonna be late!
Just hurry!
Big Bro!
Wait for me!
Hinako! Hurry!
Mom and Dad are waiting!
Good morning!
It's going to be a hot one today, isn't it?
Sorry, I gotta hit up the shop.
Okay! I'll grab a drink too!
I hate summer.
The grief...
The pain...
It brings them all back fresh to mind.
I wish summer would just
be over already.
I think there's something in the water.
A fish, maybe...?
Seems too big, though.
That's not safe.
Her eyes...
so deep and clear...
like the sea.
It's fine to gaze at the sea,
but it's not safe to lean over like that.
I-I wouldn't have fallen in.
Don't worry.
I apologize, then.
What a strange girl.
For a moment,
I thought you were preparing to throw yourself in.
Hinako.
You're the only one—
Oh?
I don't know who you are,
but don't be so rude.
I didn't mean to offend.
So sorry.
Do take care.
Hinako! Good morning!
Morning, Miko.
I'm sooooo sorry I couldn't walk with you!
What happened? You slept in?
Nah, uh... I forgot to leave my uniform out to dry
before passing out last night.
I ended up drying it
with a hairdryer.
Totally didn't think I'd make it.
You still have that cold?
Nah, I'm fine!
But let's not talk about me!
Was everything okay this morning?!
You didn't get hassled
by any creeps, did you?
Miko...
I'm not a helpless little kid.
Morning!
Miko, you're still doing this?
You're seriously so protective of Hinako.
Well, c'mon!
Hinako's kinda disaster-prone, so I worry.
Just the other day,
she tripped over nothing at all.
That's true! She's always tripping over nothing.
Right?!
You can't leave her alone!
Well...
I get how you feel, Miko, but...
Yeah. I mean...
Hinako.
Hinako?
Hinako!
What's the matter?
Nothing.
You sure?
Morning! Back to your seats, all.
Okaaay!
That day, my heart...
sank deep...
and it's lain at the bottom of the sea ever since.
The sea?
Why...
Why did I...
think she was like the sea?
Did you see Mikarin's video?
I totally did!
Hilarious, right?
We've got sectionals today, right?
Yeah... I hope I can keep up!
Aw crap, I'm late!
Hey, wait up!
This is a message from the student council.
Today's student council officer meeting will begin at 4:45 today.
Hinako!
Can we stop by the bookstore on the way back?
And the corner store!
They've got new pastries!
Sure.
Miko!
Thank goodness!
I thought you'd left already!
What's up?
Ms. Takano made some
math worksheets for the classes you missed,
and she wants you to come back to do them.
Whaaaaat!
B-But I was about to head out with Hinako...
And Mr. Yamashita wants you to go to his office
after you're done with the worksheets.
H-Hinako...
Miko...
I don't wanna go!
I hate worksheets!
And I just know Mr. Yamashita's gonna chew me out for skipping!
It'll only get worse
if you don't go sort it out.
I'll wait for you
till you're done.
Okay?
I'll finish up lickety-split, then!
Good luck!
Pull down the skirt hem...
Take off the choker...
Okay!
Sorry, Hinako!
Wait here, okay?!
I guess I'll have to find
a place to kill some time.
A classroom? Nothing to do there.
I could go to the library.
Maybe I'll read a book until Miko comes back.
What was that...
The smell of the sea.
The sound of waves crashing.
I recognize it from this morning.
Wait, what am I doing?
I'm still in my school slippers.
I'll head back.
Miko might be done by now.
That hurt.
What the...
Fou... nd...
y... ou.
Mmm, you smell so good...
What...
What's going on?
Traveling all the way here from Saikaido was well worth it.
I was interrupted this morning, but now I'll finally have you!
All of a sudden...
Wow.
I don't know what's going on.
But...
Ahh...
Now I can...
finally join you.
I told you...
it wasn't safe.
You're...
Curse you!
What's a mermaid doing here?
And how dare you stop me...
That's my prey!
Please stand behind me.
This miserable iso-onna...
Mermaid?
Iso-onna?
You sure have a lot to say
for such a bottom-feeding yokai.
That is my prey!
This girl...
belongs to me.
It was like a scene from hell itself.
I was paralyzed by the unfolding atrocity.
And yet...
I...
Hinako.
Are you all right?
How do you know my name?
Of course I know it.
I've been looking for you for so long!
For me? Just who are you?
I'm Shiori.
I came here...
to eat you.
Hinako.
Your flesh and blood is especially delicious.
That's what draws creatures like her to you.
My heart began to race...
Pathetic creatures with no sense of patience.
Deafening, like the pounding of the waves.
But you're going to become more delicious still.
So until then, I'll make sure...
to keep you safe.
Amid hollow days, permeated by
the invisible smell of an unending summer...
This girl, who appeared out of the blue, could...
She could...
Morning.
Good morning.
It's so hot!
Miko...
Hinako?! What... Why are you wet all over?!
She was fussing over me a lot yesterday after everything.
Could that have brought her cold back?
Miko's surprisingly delicate.
So rude!
I hope it doesn't get worse.
Gonna be another scorcher today.
Wanna hit the beach?
Let's grab something to eat first.
Will you...
Will you really eat me?
Do you mean it?
We'll have to see.
Oh, but I won't eat you now.
Be sure to look after those wounds.
I'll see you again.
W-Wait!
What do you mean...?
Hinako!
Hinako, you here?
Man, where'd you go?!
Miko...
Hinako!
Hey!
She's gone.
Why...
She said
that she was going to eat me.
So why did she just...
Morning! Back to your seats, all!
Ah. Before homeroom starts, let me introduce our transfer student.
The smell of...
She'll be joining our class starting today.
Of the tide... the sea...
Oumi Shiori.
I came here to eat you.
Maybe she could
make my wish come true.
Maybe...
she could let me die.
"The Sunlit Beast and the Festival Song."