♪ Dear... I send
you this LiLy! ♪
♪ As for my days... ♪
♪ they pass without
change, quietly repeating. ♪
♪ Ever since that day
everything changed. ♪
♪ As for my days... ♪
♪ My heart feels
unbearably heavy... ♪
♪ Yet my body drifts,
soft and weightless. ♪
♪ Like being drawn
toward a scent.. ♪
♪ that's just out of reach... ♪
♪ Those were the days I lived. ♪
♪ A sudden summer breeze
made white flowers sway, ♪
♪ Touching my heart,
fragile like a pouch. ♪
♪ You found me —
with those eyes. ♪
♪ Dear me... ♪
♪ The pain I've
carried so long- ♪
♪ — is it finally scattering,
scattering away? ♪
♪ The scenes you showed
me — so often beautiful... ♪
♪ They're blooming...
still blooming, even now. ♪
♪ A sea so dark it
swallows even shadows... ♪
♪ If it could cradle
the goodbyes.. ♪
♪ that lost their way...... ♪
I found myself thinking
such things... ♪
♪ But then you crossed my
mind... and I breathed again. ♪
♪ Not to the me of today — ♪
♪ but to me of that day — ♪
♪ I send this lily. ♪